Mitchell, John Papers on Microfilm 5502 mf
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Photographs (Reel 55)
  - Roosevelt Day at Wilkes-Barre, Pennsylvania. President Theodore Roosevelt accepting audience's accolades, 1905; 47 (Reel 55)
  - Roosevelt Day at Wilkes-Barre, Pennsylvania. President Theodore Roosevelt in Parade, 1905; 48 (Reel 55)
  - Roosevelt Day at Wilkes-Barre, Pennsylvania. President Theodore Roosevelt in Parade, 1905; 49 (Reel 55)
  - Roosevelt Day at Wilkes-Barre, Pennsylvania. Parade, 1905; 50 (Reel 55)
  - Roosevelt Day at Wilkes-Barre, Pennsylvania. Parade, 1905; 51 (Reel 55)
  - Theodore Roosevelt Memorial, 52 (Reel 55)
    Commemorating peaceful settlement of 1902 anthracite coal strike
  - W.C. Scott, 1899; 53 (Reel 55)
    December 23, 1899.
  - Sunnyslope, Alberta, 54 (Reel 55)
  - United Mine Workers of America. Anthracite Coal Strike of 1902., 55 (Reel 55)
    After convention had adjourned. Wilkes-Barre, Pennsylvania.
  - United Mine Workers of America. Anthracite Coal Strike of 1902., 56 (Reel 55)
    Left to right: George W. Harltein (Secretary, District 9), John Mitchell, Mr. Barrett (reporter, Scranton Truth), on way to meeting of District Executive Boards. Scranton, Pennsylvania, May 7, 1902.
  - United Mine Workers of America. Anthracite Coal Strike of 1902., 57 (Reel 55)
    "Riot" during strike. Olyphant, Pennsylvania
  - United Mine Workers of America. Anthracite Coal Strike of 1902., 58 (Reel 55)
    After a mass meeting. Scranton, Pennsylvania
  - United Mine Workers of America. Anthracite Coal Strike of 1902., 59 (Reel 55)
    Waiting to hear whether strike would be called off. Wilkes-Barre, Pennsylvania
  - United Mine Workers of America. John P. Gallagher, 1901; 60 (Reel 55)
    Secretary, District 7, UMW. March 29, 1901.
  - United Mine Workers of America. Mr. Healy, 61 (Reel 55)
    Board member, District 1, UMW.
  - United Mine Workers of America. Mass Meeting., 1903; 62 (Reel 55)
    Scranton, Pennsylvania, October 29, 1903
  - United Mine Workers of America. Miners' families, 63 (Reel 55)
  - United Mine Workers of America. John Mitchell addressing mass meeting., 1905; 64 (Reel 55)
    South Wilkes-Barre, Pennsylvania, August 18, 1905
  - United Mine Workers of America. Mass meeting hearing John Mitchell., 1905; 65 (Reel 55)
  - United Mine Workers of America. Left to right: John Mitchell, Mr. Beamish, Mr. Dunn., 1906; 66 (Reel 55)
    New York City, New York, April 9, 1906
  - United Mine Workers of America. Mitchell Day Parade., 1905; 67 (Reel 55)
    Lykens, Pennsylvania, September 20, 1905.
  - United Mine Workers of America. Mitchell Day Parade., 1905; 68 (Reel 55)
  - United Mine Workers of America. Mitchell Day Parade., 1905; 69 (Reel 55)
  - United Mine Workers of America. Mitchell Day Parade., 1905; 70 (Reel 55)
  - United Mine Workers of America. Mitchell Day Parade., 1905; 71 (Reel 55)
  - United Mine Workers of America. Mitchell Day Parade., 1905; 72 (Reel 55)
  - United Mine Workers of America. Mitchell Day Parade., 1905; 73 (Reel 55)
  - United Mine Workers of America. Mitchell Day Parade., 1905; 74 (Reel 55)
  - United Mine Workers of America. Parade., 1905; 75 (Reel 55)
  - United Mine Workers of America. Parade., 1905; 76 (Reel 55)
  - United Mine Workers of America. Parade., 1905; 77 (Reel 55)
  - United Mine Workers of America. Gathering., 1905; 78 (Reel 55)
    East Wilkes-Barre, Pennsylvania, August 21, 1905
  - United Mine Workers of America. F.H. Sherman, 79 (Reel 55)
    President, District 18, UMW
  - Charles Weger, 1898; 80 (Reel 55)
    Company L, 158 Indiana Volunteer Infantry, Spanish-American War, 1898
  - Wilkes-Barre, Pennsylvania. Public Square, 81 (Reel 55)
  - Wilkes-Barre, Pennsylvania. Scene outside city, 82 (Reel 55)
  - W. B. Wilson, 83 (Reel 55)